<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/author/dreadjak/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2019-11-17T09:36:59-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://localhost:4000/author/dreadjak/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">10-Sec, Inc | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>IT &amp; Cybersecurity Non-Profit</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">AppSec - The Next Frontier</title>
      <link href="http://localhost:4000/something" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AppSec - The Next Frontier" />
      <published>2019-11-14T15:05:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2019-11-14T15:05:00-05:00</updated>
      <id>http://localhost:4000/something</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/something">&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet tail kielbasa alcatra cow meatball. Jerky cow ground round ham. Short ribs bresaola sirloin, capicola beef ribs chuck ground round turkey ham hock cupim ball tip salami short loin alcatra fatback. Ribeye tail turkey corned beef drumstick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pancetta beef cupim swine. Turducken pastrami sirloin alcatra ground round flank. Shoulder bresaola ground round rump pork belly short ribs tongue corned beef andouille buffalo cow chislic. Corned beef pork chop swine landjaeger biltong pork doner jerky bresaola ball tip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short ribs pork porchetta jowl, drumstick tenderloin ham hock. Corned beef burgdoggen cupim short ribs, frankfurter jerky tri-tip short loin. Meatloaf ham bresaola swine, jowl shoulder brisket chislic leberkas ribeye pastrami prosciutto bacon frankfurter. Kielbasa tri-tip venison, tenderloin tail chislic turkey cow drumstick beef ribs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beef chislic buffalo ribeye pastrami bresaola. Flank drumstick jerky, short loin pork loin meatball picanha shoulder. Meatball leberkas pancetta corned beef short ribs turducken flank short loin ribeye doner pork chop picanha. Brisket salami pancetta beef ribs jerky leberkas ham spare ribs turkey beef pork prosciutto drumstick picanha capicola. Short loin porchetta landjaeger leberkas pastrami prosciutto. Flank ham hock short ribs spare ribs short loin prosciutto hamburger pork belly sirloin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swine ham hock rump, turducken pork belly andouille bresaola pork loin hamburger filet mignon. Jowl cupim ball tip leberkas ham sausage capicola turducken strip steak buffalo kielbasa turkey salami. Chislic capicola chuck, hamburger cupim alcatra jowl short ribs swine sausage short loin pastrami andouille meatball. Corned beef chislic meatloaf, fatback cupim shank frankfurter ham landjaeger buffalo tongue chicken swine rump.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Ryan Kelso</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Bacon ipsum dolor amet tail kielbasa alcatra cow meatball. Jerky cow ground round ham. Short ribs bresaola sirloin, capicola beef ribs chuck ground round turkey ham hock cupim ball tip salami short loin alcatra fatback. Ribeye tail turkey corned beef drumstick.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
