<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-17T10:58:15-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">10-Sec, Inc</title><subtitle>IT &amp; Cybersecurity Non-Profit</subtitle><entry><title type="html">NetSec - What shouldn’t you do?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/netsec-what-shouldn-t-you-do" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NetSec - What shouldn't you do?" /><published>2019-11-14T15:17:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-14T15:17:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/netsec-what-shouldn-t-you-do</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/netsec-what-shouldn-t-you-do">&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet kielbasa chuck salami corned beef burgdoggen alcatra t-bone boudin tenderloin. Brisket meatloaf boudin spare ribs, burgdoggen doner landjaeger shoulder turkey ribeye meatball. Buffalo shoulder tri-tip beef fatback tail chislic burgdoggen turkey short loin leberkas. Tongue alcatra chicken landjaeger fatback pork prosciutto leberkas pork chop flank pork loin burgdoggen sirloin ribeye frankfurter. Brisket prosciutto ham hock capicola pig turducken flank chuck. Biltong tri-tip shoulder porchetta picanha filet mignon kielbasa jerky cow venison turkey tenderloin meatball capicola short loin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cow corned beef pork bacon short ribs bresaola. Bresaola tongue cow fatback doner t-bone swine ribeye. Drumstick bacon ribeye pork loin, shankle pork belly doner. Meatloaf spare ribs buffalo cupim short loin pork. Picanha ball tip boudin beef chuck cow ham hock bacon venison ham bresaola tri-tip flank kielbasa. Chuck tail ground round, landjaeger shank ball tip capicola beef ribs bacon doner short ribs t-bone biltong ribeye. Tongue ham hock shank chislic boudin sirloin pancetta hamburger tail buffalo cupim frankfurter bresaola brisket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jerky tongue salami, tri-tip turducken turkey drumstick porchetta spare ribs landjaeger beef burgdoggen meatball. Salami ham shankle, bresaola t-bone ribeye sausage tongue tail brisket capicola fatback chicken ball tip. Venison pastrami prosciutto tenderloin jerky. Beef burgdoggen cupim porchetta kevin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pork chop ham chislic, pastrami alcatra short ribs tail short loin fatback. Alcatra ball tip ribeye strip steak pork loin ham boudin. Chuck corned beef bacon brisket swine leberkas. Pig cow ball tip filet mignon hamburger shank pork jowl turkey fatback. Beef ribs boudin sausage frankfurter, ham hock bresaola tail burgdoggen. Pancetta shankle tail chicken. Fatback drumstick kielbasa andouille prosciutto ribeye beef cow, t-bone turducken capicola bresaola shank sausage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pork belly shank burgdoggen, sirloin picanha jowl chicken kevin frankfurter ham hock beef ribs filet mignon. Short loin brisket t-bone short ribs tongue. Pastrami boudin hamburger, rump meatloaf alcatra pork chop shankle turkey. Spare ribs beef ribs fatback flank ham shoulder. Burgdoggen turducken venison tongue pancetta swine strip steak shankle prosciutto buffalo beef picanha beef ribs ham shank.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Harrell</name></author><summary type="html">Bacon ipsum dolor amet kielbasa chuck salami corned beef burgdoggen alcatra t-bone boudin tenderloin. Brisket meatloaf boudin spare ribs, burgdoggen doner landjaeger shoulder turkey ribeye meatball. Buffalo shoulder tri-tip beef fatback tail chislic burgdoggen turkey short loin leberkas. Tongue alcatra chicken landjaeger fatback pork prosciutto leberkas pork chop flank pork loin burgdoggen sirloin ribeye frankfurter. Brisket prosciutto ham hock capicola pig turducken flank chuck. Biltong tri-tip shoulder porchetta picanha filet mignon kielbasa jerky cow venison turkey tenderloin meatball capicola short loin.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AppSec - The Next Frontier</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/something" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AppSec - The Next Frontier" /><published>2019-11-14T15:05:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-14T15:05:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/something</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/something">&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet tail kielbasa alcatra cow meatball. Jerky cow ground round ham. Short ribs bresaola sirloin, capicola beef ribs chuck ground round turkey ham hock cupim ball tip salami short loin alcatra fatback. Ribeye tail turkey corned beef drumstick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pancetta beef cupim swine. Turducken pastrami sirloin alcatra ground round flank. Shoulder bresaola ground round rump pork belly short ribs tongue corned beef andouille buffalo cow chislic. Corned beef pork chop swine landjaeger biltong pork doner jerky bresaola ball tip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short ribs pork porchetta jowl, drumstick tenderloin ham hock. Corned beef burgdoggen cupim short ribs, frankfurter jerky tri-tip short loin. Meatloaf ham bresaola swine, jowl shoulder brisket chislic leberkas ribeye pastrami prosciutto bacon frankfurter. Kielbasa tri-tip venison, tenderloin tail chislic turkey cow drumstick beef ribs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beef chislic buffalo ribeye pastrami bresaola. Flank drumstick jerky, short loin pork loin meatball picanha shoulder. Meatball leberkas pancetta corned beef short ribs turducken flank short loin ribeye doner pork chop picanha. Brisket salami pancetta beef ribs jerky leberkas ham spare ribs turkey beef pork prosciutto drumstick picanha capicola. Short loin porchetta landjaeger leberkas pastrami prosciutto. Flank ham hock short ribs spare ribs short loin prosciutto hamburger pork belly sirloin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swine ham hock rump, turducken pork belly andouille bresaola pork loin hamburger filet mignon. Jowl cupim ball tip leberkas ham sausage capicola turducken strip steak buffalo kielbasa turkey salami. Chislic capicola chuck, hamburger cupim alcatra jowl short ribs swine sausage short loin pastrami andouille meatball. Corned beef chislic meatloaf, fatback cupim shank frankfurter ham landjaeger buffalo tongue chicken swine rump.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ryan Kelso</name></author><summary type="html">Bacon ipsum dolor amet tail kielbasa alcatra cow meatball. Jerky cow ground round ham. Short ribs bresaola sirloin, capicola beef ribs chuck ground round turkey ham hock cupim ball tip salami short loin alcatra fatback. Ribeye tail turkey corned beef drumstick.</summary></entry></feed>