<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="/author/n2o/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2019-11-17T10:27:36-05:00</updated>
  <id>/author/n2o/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">10-Sec, Inc | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>IT &amp; Cybersecurity Non-Profit</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">NetSec - What shouldn’t you do?</title>
      <link href="/netsec-what-shouldn-t-you-do" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NetSec - What shouldn't you do?" />
      <published>2019-11-14T15:17:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2019-11-14T15:17:00-05:00</updated>
      <id>/netsec-what-shouldn-t-you-do</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/netsec-what-shouldn-t-you-do">&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet kielbasa chuck salami corned beef burgdoggen alcatra t-bone boudin tenderloin. Brisket meatloaf boudin spare ribs, burgdoggen doner landjaeger shoulder turkey ribeye meatball. Buffalo shoulder tri-tip beef fatback tail chislic burgdoggen turkey short loin leberkas. Tongue alcatra chicken landjaeger fatback pork prosciutto leberkas pork chop flank pork loin burgdoggen sirloin ribeye frankfurter. Brisket prosciutto ham hock capicola pig turducken flank chuck. Biltong tri-tip shoulder porchetta picanha filet mignon kielbasa jerky cow venison turkey tenderloin meatball capicola short loin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cow corned beef pork bacon short ribs bresaola. Bresaola tongue cow fatback doner t-bone swine ribeye. Drumstick bacon ribeye pork loin, shankle pork belly doner. Meatloaf spare ribs buffalo cupim short loin pork. Picanha ball tip boudin beef chuck cow ham hock bacon venison ham bresaola tri-tip flank kielbasa. Chuck tail ground round, landjaeger shank ball tip capicola beef ribs bacon doner short ribs t-bone biltong ribeye. Tongue ham hock shank chislic boudin sirloin pancetta hamburger tail buffalo cupim frankfurter bresaola brisket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jerky tongue salami, tri-tip turducken turkey drumstick porchetta spare ribs landjaeger beef burgdoggen meatball. Salami ham shankle, bresaola t-bone ribeye sausage tongue tail brisket capicola fatback chicken ball tip. Venison pastrami prosciutto tenderloin jerky. Beef burgdoggen cupim porchetta kevin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pork chop ham chislic, pastrami alcatra short ribs tail short loin fatback. Alcatra ball tip ribeye strip steak pork loin ham boudin. Chuck corned beef bacon brisket swine leberkas. Pig cow ball tip filet mignon hamburger shank pork jowl turkey fatback. Beef ribs boudin sausage frankfurter, ham hock bresaola tail burgdoggen. Pancetta shankle tail chicken. Fatback drumstick kielbasa andouille prosciutto ribeye beef cow, t-bone turducken capicola bresaola shank sausage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pork belly shank burgdoggen, sirloin picanha jowl chicken kevin frankfurter ham hock beef ribs filet mignon. Short loin brisket t-bone short ribs tongue. Pastrami boudin hamburger, rump meatloaf alcatra pork chop shankle turkey. Spare ribs beef ribs fatback flank ham shoulder. Burgdoggen turducken venison tongue pancetta swine strip steak shankle prosciutto buffalo beef picanha beef ribs ham shank.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>James Harrell</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Bacon ipsum dolor amet kielbasa chuck salami corned beef burgdoggen alcatra t-bone boudin tenderloin. Brisket meatloaf boudin spare ribs, burgdoggen doner landjaeger shoulder turkey ribeye meatball. Buffalo shoulder tri-tip beef fatback tail chislic burgdoggen turkey short loin leberkas. Tongue alcatra chicken landjaeger fatback pork prosciutto leberkas pork chop flank pork loin burgdoggen sirloin ribeye frankfurter. Brisket prosciutto ham hock capicola pig turducken flank chuck. Biltong tri-tip shoulder porchetta picanha filet mignon kielbasa jerky cow venison turkey tenderloin meatball capicola short loin.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
